A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 2 FA1137
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation records, Grants, Series 2
1979-2001
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation
FA1137
43.03 Cubic Feet 112 letter document boxes and 1 legal box.
Biographical/Historical Note
The John A. Hartford Foundation (JAHF) was established in 1929 by brothers John and George Hartford, sons of the founder of the Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company (A&P). The foundation is a private, nonpartisan philanthropy dedicated to improving the care of older adults. For its first several decades, the foundation broadly supported clinical medical research. By 1982, it began to focus solely on geriatric healthcare. In 2015, JAHF paid out $20.2 million on a total of 80 active grants and committed $25.3 million to 24 new grants projects, all focused on the care of older adults.
Conditions Governing Access Note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents Note
The collection contains grant files and associated administrative records from 1979 to 2001.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The John A. Hartford Foundation records were donated to RAC by JAHF in 2014. Record transfers to RAC began in 2014 and continue as needed.
Arrangement
Arranged as received.
Other Finding Aids
For Series 1 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA771/collection
For Series 3 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1218/collection
For Series 4 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1296/collection
For Series 5 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1297/collection
For Series 6 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1326/collection
For Series 7 of the John A. Hartford Foundation records, see http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1138/collection
- Grants, 2
  - University of California Los Angeles: R. Brook (no grant number), 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 869-870)
  - Vanderbilt University: W. Ray (89-309), 1989-1993 (Box 126, Folder 871-873)
  - Yale Schol of Medicine: L. Cooney (88-345), 1988-1993 (Box 126, Folder 874-875)
  - Yale Schol of Medicine: L. Cooney (88-345), 1988-1993 (Box 127, Folder 876-877)
  - Benton International: Contracts (CHM/FAP), 1991-1992 (Box 127, Folder 878-882)
  - Benton International: Contracts (CHM/FAP), 1992-1993 (Box 128, Folder 883-888)
  - Benton International: Contracts (CHM/FAP), 1994 (Box 129, Folder 889-890)
  - George Washington University, National Health Policy Forum: J. Miller Jones (83-056), 1983-1986 (Box 129, Folder 891-895)
  - George Washington University: W. Knauss (87-267), 1987-1991 (Box 130, Folder 896-903)
  - Harvard Medical School: B. McNeil (79-021), 1979-1986 (Box 131, Folder 904-910)
  - Harvard University: L. Lipsitz (87-398), 1987-1992 (Box 131, Folder 911-912)
  - Harvard University: L. Lipsitz (87-398), 1987-1992 (Box 132, Folder 913-914)
  - Johns Hopkins University: J. Burton (88-007), 1988-1992 (Box 132, Folder 915-921)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine: J. Burton (91-011), 1991-1995 (Box 133, Folder 922-924)
  - University of Minnesota: T. Choi (86-122), 1986-1990 (Box 133, Folder 925-928)
  - University of Minnesota: T. Choi (86-122), 1986-1990 (Box 134, Folder 929)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Wasson (86-121), 1986-1989 (Box 134, Folder 930-935)
  - Sharp HealthCare: S. Salisbury (89-130), 1989-1993 (Box 135, Folder 936-943)
  - Sharp HealthCare (CA): S. Salisbury (89-130), 1989-1993 (Box 136, Folder 944-949)
  - University of Southern California: B. Williams (88-186), 1988-1994 (Box 137, Folder 950-957)
  - Minnesota Institute for Community Health Information: D. Shaller (93-142), 1993-1995 (Box 138, Folder 958-960)
  - Minnesota Institute for Community Health Information: D. Shaller (95-108), 1995-1999 (Box 138, Folder 961-963)
  - Minnesota Institute for Community Health Information: D. Shaller (95-108), 1995-1999 (Box 139, Folder 964-968)
  - Minnesota Institute for Community Health Information: D. Shaller (93-142), 1993-1995 (Box 139, Folder 969)
  - Minnesota Institute for Community Health Information: D. Shaller (95-108), 1995-1999 (Box 140, Folder 970-973)
  - Ohio Corporation for Health Information: W. Petrarca (94-114) (Box 140, Folder 974)
  - Foundation for Health Care Quality (NRC): R. Rubin (94-028), 1994-1999 (Box 140, Folder 975-977)
  - Foundation for Health Care Quality (NRC): R. Rubin (94-028), 1994-1999 (Box 141, Folder 978-980)
  - Carter Center: E. Hutchins (88-214), 1988-1996 (Box 141, Folder 981-984)
  - Carter Center: E. Hutchins (88-214), 1988-1996 (Box 142, Folder 985-990)
    - Carter Center (88-214): Separated media "Health Risk Appraisal for Older People, Version 1.0", 1992 May 31; 2014:023:013; 3 diskettes: software, documentation, and backup (Box 2014:023:013, Folder 990)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
    - Carter Center (88-214): Separated media "HRAOP Documentation Backup" (Box 142)
    - Carter Center (88-214): Separated media "HRAOP QUEX" (Box 142)
  - National Foundation For Facial Reconstruction: R. Bochat (86-227), 1986-1990 (Box 143, Folder 991-994)
  - National Foundation For Facial Reconstruction: R. Bochat (89-275), 1989-1992 (Box 143, Folder 995-996)
  - University of Texas Southwestern: R. Wasserman (84-401-1), 1984-1988 (Box 143, Folder 997)
  - University of Texas Southwestern: Lipsky (84-401-2), 1984-1989 (Box 143, Folder 998)
  - University of Texas Southwestern: Grundy (84-401-3), 1984-1989 (Box 143, Folder 999)
  - University of Texas Southwestern: Norgard (84-401-4), 1984-1989 (Box 143, Folder 1000)
  - University of Texas Southwestern: Capra (84-401-5), 1984-1988 (Box 143, Folder 1001)
  - University of Texas Southwestern: Cuthbert (84-401-6), 1984-1989 (Box 143, Folder 1002)
  - University of Texas Southwestern: Nunnally (84-401-7), 1984-1990 (Box 144, Folder 1003)
  - University of Texas Southwestern: Sontheimer (84-401-8), 1984-1989 (Box 144, Folder 1004)
  - University of Texas Southwestern: Hagler (84-401-9), 1984-1989 (Box 144, Folder 1005)
  - University of Texas Southwestern: Brown (84-401-10), 1984-1988 (Box 144, Folder 1006)
  - University of Texas Southwestern (84-401-0), 1984-1990 (Box 144, Folder 1007-1010)
    - University of Texas Southwestern: Separated photographs (84-401-0), c. 1988; 2013:023:014; 3 prints, 1 slide of staff (Box 2014:023:014, Folder 1008)
  - Mayo Foundation: F. Nobrega (83-061), 1983-1985 (Box 145, Folder 1011-1014)
  - Mayo Foundation: F. Nobrega (85-235), 1985-1992 (Box 145, Folder 1015-1019)
  - Mayo Foundation: F. Nobrega (85-235), 1985-1992 (Box 146, Folder 1020-1021)
  - Minnesota Coalition on Health: P. Drury (88-037), 1988-1991 (Box 146, Folder 1022-1028)
  - Minnesota Coalition on Health: P. Drury (88-037), 1988-1991 (Box 147, Folder 1029-1030)
  - Community Health Management (CHM), 1992-1994 (Box 147, Folder 1031)
  - CHM: New Direction for Policy, 1992 (Box 147, Folder 1032)
  - CHM: Clark Havighurst, 1992 (Box 147, Folder 1033-1036)
  - CHM: Clark Havighurst, 1992 (Box 148, Folder 1037)
  - CHM: ACLU, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 1038-1039)
  - CHM: Harvard Medical School, 1992 (Box 148, Folder 1040)
  - CHM: Fenton Communications, 1992 (Box 148, Folder 1041-1042)
  - CHM: Colorado CHMIS, Inc: R. Pollack, 1992-1994 (Box 148, Folder 1043)
  - CHM: Greater Detroit Area Health Council: J. Kenny, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 1044)
  - CHM: Hawaii Department of Health: J. Lewin, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 1045)
  - CHM: Maryland Alliance for Healthcare: D.S. Hillier, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 1046)
  - Statewide Health Information Network (SHINE) of West Virginia: P. Cline (93-240), 1993 (Box 149, Folder 1047)
  - Cleveland Tomorrow: J. Morley (90-290), 1990-1994 (Box 149, Folder 1048-1053)
  - Cleveland Tomorrow: J. Morley (90-290), 1990-1994 (Box 150, Folder 1054-1061)
  - Cleveland Tomorrow: J. Morley (90-290), 1990-1994 (Box 151, Folder 1062-1067)
  - Midwest Business Group on Health: J. Mortimer (87-067), 1987-1989 (Box 152, Folder 1068-1075)
  - Midwest Business Group on Health: J. Mortimer (87-067), 1987-1989 (Box 153, Folder 1076-1078)
  - Midwest Business Group on Health: J. Mortimer (88-281), 1988-1993 (Box 153, Folder 1079-1084)
  - Midwest Business Group on Health: J. Mortimer (88-281), 1988-1993 (Box 154, Folder 1085-1092)
  - Grantmakers in Health: C. McDermott (85-016), 1985-1986 (Box 155, Folder 1093-1095)
  - Grantmakers in Health: C. McDermott (87-165), 1987-1989 (Box 155, Folder 1096-1099)
  - Grantmakers in Health: C. McDermott (89-114), 1989-1990 (Box 155, Folder 1100-1102)
  - Grantmakers in Health: C. McDermott (89-114), 1989-1990 (Box 156, Folder 1103-1104)
  - Grantmakers in Health: C. McDermott (90-112), 1990-1992 (Box 156, Folder 1105-1107)
  - Grantmakers in Health: C. McDermott (91-134), 1991-1993 (Box 156, Folder 1108-1109)
  - The Foundation Center: T. Buckman, 1983-1986 (Box 157, Folder 1110)
  - The Foundation Center: T. Buckman (88-158), 1988-1989 (Box 157, Folder 1111)
  - The Foundation Center: T. Buckman (89-148), 1989-1990 (Box 157, Folder 1112)
  - The Foundation Center: T. Buckman (89-318), 1989-1991 (Box 157, Folder 1113-1114)
  - The Foundation Center: T. Buckman (90-137), 1990 (Box 157, Folder 1115)
  - The Foundation Center: S. Engelhardt (91-133), 1991-1993 (Box 157, Folder 1116-1118)
  - Central Park Conservancy: J. Parks (89-234), 1989-1990 (Box 158, Folder 1119)
  - United Hospital Fund: W. Nolen (89-326), 1989-1991 (Box 158, Folder 1120)
  - Environmental Learning Center: S. Adams (92-236), 1992 (Box 158, Folder 1121)
  - University of Rochester: P. Griner (84-313), 1984-1988 (Box 158, Folder 1122-1126)
  - University of Rochester Medical Center: R. Panzer (88-146), 1988-1994 (Box 158, Folder 1127-1128)
  - University of Rochester Medical Center: R. Panzer (88-146), 1988-1994 (Box 159, Folder 1129-1135)
  - University of Rochester Medical Center: R. Panzer (88-146), 1988-1994 (Box 160, Folder 1136-1137)
  - Brigham and Women's Hospital: B. McNeil (88-175), 1988-1992 (Box 160, Folder 1138-1142)
  - Brigham and Women's Hospital: B. McNeil (88-175), 1988-1992 (Box 161, Folder 1143-1145)
  - Beth Israel Hospital: D. Calkins (88-124), 1988-1994 (Box 161, Folder 1146-1149)
  - Beth Israel Hospital: D. Calkins (88-124), 1988-1994 (Box 162, Folder 1150-1154)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Wennberg (82-570), 1982-1985 (Box 162, Folder 1155-1156)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Wennberg (82-570), 1982-1985 (Box 163, Folder 1157-1161)
  - Dartmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center: H. Sox (88-298), 1988-1993 (Box 163, Folder 1162-1164)
  - Dartmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center: H. Sox (88-298), 1988-1993 (Box 164, Folder 1165-1170)
  - The George Washington University, National Health Policy Forum: M. Ein (82-520), 1982-1985 (Box 165, Folder 1171-1176)
  - Overlook Hospital: J. Gregory (85-046), 1985-1986 (Box 165, Folder 1177)
  - Older Americans Consumer Cooperative: J. Firman (84-168), 1984-1986 (Box 166, Folder 1178-1180)
  - Palo Alto Medical Foundation: A. Scitovsky (82-519), 1982-1986 (Box 166, Folder 1181-1185)
  - Palo Alto Medical Foundation: A. Scitovsky (82-519), 1982-1986 (Box 167, Folder 1186-1188)
  - Rochester Area Hospital Corp.: J. Block (79-001), 1979-1982 (Box 167, Folder 1189-1192)
  - Rochester Area Hospital Corp.: J. Block (80-000), 1980-1982 (Box 167, Folder 1193)
  - Rochester Area Hospital Corp.: J. Block (82-000), 1982-1983 (Box 167, Folder 1194)
  - Kaiser Permanente SoCal Medical: R. Della Penna (95-207), 1995-1998 (Box 168, Folder 1195-1200)
  - Kaiser Permanente SoCal Medical: R. Della Penna (97-028), 1997-1999 (Box 169, Folder 1201-1203)
  - Bethany College: D. Cummins (94-292), 1994-1995 (Box 169, Folder 1204)
  - Brooks School: L. Becker (98-357), 1994-1995 (Box 169, Folder 1205)
  - Brandeis University: P. Mutschler (96-196), 1996-2000 (Box 169, Folder 1206-1208)
  - Brandeis University: P. Mutschler (96-196), 1996-2000 (Box 170, Folder 1209-1213)
  - Central Park Conservancy: M. Purnell (95-107), 1995-1997 (Box 170, Folder 1214)
  - Central Park Conservancy: K. Putnam (97-390), 1997-1998 (Box 170, Folder 1215)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP): Pine and Associates/Benton International, Community Health Management Institute (90-220), 1990-1992 (Box 171, Folder 1216-1220)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP): CHMIS (91-282), 1991-1993 (Box 171, Folder 1221-1222)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP): CHMIS (91-282), 1991-1993 (Box 172, Folder 1223-1227)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP): CHMIS (92-318), 1992-1994 (Box 172, Folder 1228-1230)
  - Foundation-Administered Project (FAP): CHMIS (92-318), 1992-1994 (Box 173, Folder 1231-1232)
  - New England Medical Center: P. Van Etten (84-056), 1984-1987 (Box 173, Folder 1233-1238)
  - New England Medical Center: P. Van Etten (84-056), 1984-1987 (Box 174, Folder 1239)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals: S. Pauker (87-269), 1987-1992 (Box 174, Folder 1240-1244)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals: S. Pauker (87-269), 1987-1992 (Box 175, Folder 1245-1246)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals: J. Ware (89-296), 1989-1993 (Box 175, Folder 1247-1251)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals: J. Ware (89-296), 1989-1993 (Box 176, Folder 1252-1255)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: R. Brook (83-172), 1983-1989 (Box 176, Folder 1256-1257)
  - National Association of Health Data Organizations: M. Larks (86-375), 1986-1989 (Box 177, Folder 1258-1263)
  - National Association of Health Data Organizations: M. Larks (86-375), 1986-1989 (Box 178, Folder 1264-1266)
  - Harvard Medical School: L. Lipsitz (91-005), 1991-1995 (Box 178, Folder 1267-1268)
  - St. Louis University Medical Center: J. Morley (91-051), 1991-1995 (Box 178, Folder 1269-1270)
  - St. Louis University Medical Center: J. Morley (91-051), 1991-1995 (Box 179, Folder 1271-1273)
  - University of Michigan Medical Center: J. Halter (91-039), 1991-1995 (Box 179, Folder 1274-1276)
  - University of Michigan Medical Center (Coordinating Center): J. Halter (91-106), 1991-1995 (Box 179, Folder 1277-1279)
  - University of Michigan Medical Center (Coordinating Center): J. Halter (91-106), 1991-1995 (Box 180, Folder 1280-1285)
  - University of Pennsylvania School of Medicine: A. Pack (91-009), 1991-1995 (Box 180, Folder 1286)
  - University of Pennsylvania School of Medicine: A. Pack (91-009), 1991-1995 (Box 181, Folder 1287-1289)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: W. Neaves (84-401), 1984-1994 (Box 181, Folder 1290-1294)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: W. Neaves (84-401), 1984-1994 (Box 182, Folder 1295-1301)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: W. Neaves (84-401), 1984-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1301-1304)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Lipton (84-401-11), 1984-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1305)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Sambrook (84-401-12), 1984-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1306)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Thiele/Lipsky (84-401-13), 1984-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1307)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: WIlson (84-401-14), 1984-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1308)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Grundy (84-401-15), 1984-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1309)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Ozanne (84-401-16), 1984-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1310)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Hansen/Radolf (84-401-17), 1984-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1311)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Estabrook (84-401-18), 1984-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1312)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Haley/Jones (84-401-19), 1984-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1313)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Vitetta/Uhr (84-401-20A), 1984-1994 (Box 184, Folder 1314)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Vitetta/Uhr (84-401-20B), 1984-1994 (Box 184, Folder 1315)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Antich/Kulkarni (84-401-21), 1984-1994 (Box 184, Folder 1316)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Butow (84-401-22), 1984-1994 (Box 184, Folder 1317)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Lipsky/Thiele (84-401-23), 1984-1994 (Box 184, Folder 1318)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Norgard/Radolf (84-401-24), 1984-1994 (Box 184, Folder 1319)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Ross/Higashijima (84-401-25), 1984-1994 (Box 184, Folder 1320)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Chubb (84-401-26), 1984-1994 (Box 184, Folder 1321)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center: Faber/Peshock (84-401-27), 1984-1994 (Box 184, Folder 1322)
  - Rochester Area Hospitals: J. Block (no grant number), 1980-1982 (Box 184, Folder 1323-1326)
  - Rochester Area Hospitals: J. Block (no grant number), 1980-1982 (Box 185, Folder 1327-1328)
  - InterStudy: D. Aquilina (no grant number), 1980-1982 (Box 185, Folder 1329-1333)
  - InterStudy: D. Aquilina (no grant number), 1980-1982 (Box 186, Folder 1334)
  - Classroom, Inc.: L. Bernard (95-341), 1995-1997 (Box 186, Folder 1335-1336)
  - Classroom, Inc.: L. Bernard (98-290), 1998-2000 (Box 186, Folder 1337)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Wasson (92-298), 1992-1998 (Box 186, Folder 1338)
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Wasson (92-298), 1992-1998 (Box 187, Folder 1339-1344)
    - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Wasson (92-298) Separated media "The CCEA Approach", 1993; 2014:023:015; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11153)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instructions.
  - Dartmouth Medical School: J. Wasson (92-298), 1992-1998 (Box 188, Folder 1346-1348)
  - University of North Carolina: M. Williams (89-162), 1989-1992 (Box 188, Folder 1349-1352)
  - University of Pennsylvania: R. Lavizzo-Mourey (97-261), 1997-2000 (Box 189, Folder 1353)
  - University of Rochester: W. Hall (94-160), 1994-1999 (Box 189, Folder 1354-1357)
  - Vanderbilt University: W. Ray (89-309), 1989-1993 (Box 189, Folder 1358-1359)
  - Vanderbilt University: W. Ray (89-309), 1989-1993 (Box 190, Folder 1360-1366)
  - University of Michigan: J. Halter (87-399), 1987-1992 (Box 191, Folder 1367-1370)
  - University of Michigan: J. Halter (89-300), 1989-1992 (Box 191, Folder 1371-1372)
  - University of Michigan: J. Halter (90-212), 1990-1992 (Box 191, Folder 1373-1374)
  - University of Michigan: J. Halter (90-212), 1990-1992 (Box 192, Folder 1375-1378)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: J. Beck (87-384), 1987-1993 (Box 192, Folder 1379-1380)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: J. Beck (87-384), 1987-1993 (Box 193, Folder 1381-1383)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: D. Reuben (91-010), 1991-1995 (Box 193, Folder 1384-1387)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: D. Reuben (91-010), 1991-1995 (Box 194, Folder 1388-1390)
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine: M. Miller (87-400), 1987-1991 (Box 194, Folder 1391-1393)
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine: M. Miller (87-400), 1987-1991 (Box 195, Folder 1394-1399)
  - Mount Sinai School of Medicine: M. Miller (91-007), 1991-1995 (Box 196, Folder 1400-1403)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: R. Brook (87-266), 1987-1991 (Box 196, Folder 1404-1407)
  - University of California, Los Angeles: R. Brook (87-266), 1987-1991 (Box 197, Folder 1408-1409)
  - University of Arkansas: D. Lipschitz (97-248), 1997-2000 (Box 197, Folder 1410)
  - University Hospitals of Cleveland: P. Anderson (92-307), 1992-1996 (Box 197, Folder 1411-1415)
  - University of Maryland at Baltimore: H. Goldman (96-225), 1996-1999 (Box 198, Folder 1416-1422)
  - Medications Program: Meeting, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 1423)
  - Medications Program: Request for Proposals (RFP) file, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 1424)
  - Medications Program: RFP applicants, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 1425)
  - Medications Program: RFP inquires, 1985 (Box 199, Folder 1426)
  - Medications Program: Marketing, 1985 (Box 199, Folder 1427)
  - Medications Program: Articles, 1984-1985 (Box 199, Folder 1428)
  - Medications Program: Correspondence after declinations, 1986 April (Box 199, Folder 1429)
  - Medications Program: Memo of recommended grants, 1986 April (Box 199, Folder 1430)
  - Medications Program: Notice of award, 1986 May (Box 199, Folder 1431)
  - Medications Program: Memo on projected plans, 1986 June (Box 199, Folder 1432)
  - Medications Program: Meeting on RFPs, 1987 April (Box 199, Folder 1433)
  - Medications Program: Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 199, Folder 1434)
  - Medications Program: Meeting, 1986 June (Box 199, Folder 1435)
  - Medications Program: Meeting, 1986 June (Box 199, Folder 1436)
  - Medications Program: Meeting notes, 1986 June (Box 199, Folder 1437)
  - Medications Program: Program evaluation, 1989 May (Box 199, Folder 1438)
  - Medications Program: Second intitiative, 1989 January (Box 199, Folder 1439)
  - Medications Program: Second intitiative, 1987-1989 (Box 199, Folder 1440)
  - Medications Program: Meeting, 1989 November (Box 200, Folder 1441)
  - Medications Program: Committee rankings for proposals, 1989 (Box 200, Folder 1442)
  - Medications Program: Bibliographies, 1989 (Box 200, Folder 1443)
  - Medications Program: Meeting, 1989 December (Box 200, Folder 1444)
  - Medications Program: Meeting, 1989 December (Box 200, Folder 1445)
  - Medications Program: Symposium, 1989 November (Box 200, Folder 1446)
  - Medications Program: Primary and secondary reviews of applications, 1989 (Box 200, Folder 1447)
  - Medications Program: Background material, 1989 (Box 200, Folder 1448)
  - Medications Program: Committee members, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 1449)
  - Medications Program: Jerry Avorn, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 1450)
  - Medications Program: Marshall Becker, 1985-1986 (Box 200, Folder 1451)
  - Medications Program: Wayne Ray, 1985-1986 (Box 200, Folder 1452)
  - Medications Program: Rosalie Kane, 1985-1986 (Box 201, Folder 1453)
  - Medications Program: Ian Lawson, 1985-1986 (Box 201, Folder 1454)
  - Medications Program: Mathy Mezey, 1985-1986 (Box 201, Folder 1455)
  - Medications Program: Nuala Pell, 1986 (Box 201, Folder 1456)
  - Medications Program: John Rowe, 1985-1986 (Box 201, Folder 1457)
  - Medications Program: Neville Strumpf, 1986 (Box 201, Folder 1458)
  - Medications Program: Helene Lipton, 1985-1986 (Box 201, Folder 1459)
  - Medications Program: Jere Goyan, 1985-1986 (Box 201, Folder 1460)
  - Medications Program: Rankings for Top 10 proposals, 1985 (Box 201, Folder 1461)
  - Medications Program: Background material, 1986-1988 (Box 201, Folder 1462)
  - Medications Program: Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 201, Folder 1463)
  - Medications Program: Background material, 1983-1986 (Box 201, Folder 1464)
  - Stanford University School of Medicine: G. Reaven/C. Winograd (91-052), 1991-1996 (Box 201, Folder 1465-1468)
  - Stanford University School of Medicine: G. Reaven/C. Winograd (91-052), 1991-1996 (Box 202, Folder 1469-1474)